const quiz = [
	{
		question: 'Where does the sun rises from?',
		option: ['East', 'West', 'North', 'South'],
		correctAnswer: 'East'
	},
	{
		question: 'The capital of Nepal ?',
		option: ['Pokhara', 'Chitwan', 'Lumbini', 'Kathmandu'],
		correctAnswer: 'Kathmandu'
	},
	{
		question: 'National animal of Nepal?',
		option: ['Cow', 'Buffalo', 'Goat', 'Dog'],
		correctAnswer: 'Cow'
	},
	{
		question: 'How many district there in Nepal?',
		option: ['76', '73', '77', '78'],
		correctAnswer: '77'
	},
	{
		question: 'How many kidney in human?',
		option: ['1', '3', '4', '2'],
		correctAnswer: '2'
	},
	{
		question: 'Where is Mt Everest located?',
		option: ['India', 'China', 'Nepal', 'Bhutan'],
		correctAnswer: 'Nepal'
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the currency of Nepal?',
		option: ['Rs', 'USD', 'Nrs', 'Yen'],
		correctAnswer: 'Nrs'
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the bike Sanju Dai wants to buy?',
		option: ['Royal Enfield', 'CRF', 'Honda', 'Rx100'],
		correctAnswer: 'Royal Enfield'
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the salary Sanju Dai have?',
		option: ['0', '100', '1000', '10000'],
		correctAnswer: '0'
	},
	{
		question: 'What is the binary of ON?',
		option: ['0', '1', '10', '11'],
		correctAnswer: '1'
	},

]


export { quiz};